

Profile

Since 2018 I have been professionally engaged in SharePoint development and support, mainly dealing with Fronted. My work involves using multiple programming languages such as JavaScript, Type Script, HTML and CSS, and libraries like React, VUE and Bootstrap

Employment History

Junior SharePoint Engineer at SolidBrain, Kraków

August 2019 — Present

- Active participation in product design reviews by providing creative and practical ideas and solutions in a teamwork.
- Design, develop and maintain key components of the SharePoint by using JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Vue.js and React.JS.
- · Testing and debugging code.
- Creating software documentations.
- Writing Units Tests.

Application Specialist at Solidbrain, Kraków

December 2018 — August 2019

- Support and administration of SharePoint Server 2013.
- Fulfilling business requirements and proposing solution adjusted to needs
- Manage escalations reported by the internal users.
- · Participation in SCRUM ceremony.

Customer Service Specialist and Seller at ABM Włodarczyk Ubezpieczenia (Insurance Office), Kraków

June 2017 — November 2019

- · Insurance selling.
- · Solving problems of customers.
- · Creating and managing database of clients.

Education

Post-diploma studies in Programming of Web Application , AGH University of Science and Technology, Kraków

October 2020 — June 2021

Master degree in Chemical Engineering, Cracow University of Science,

March 2016 — June 2018

Bachelor of Chemical Engineering, Cracow University of Science, Kraków October 2012 — February 2016

Details

M. Langiewicza 24, Kraków, 31-425, Poland, 533261323

jagoda.bieniek1234@gmail.com

Date of birth

04-06-1993

Skills

JavaScript

TypeScript

VUE JS

React JS

jQuery

Bootstrap 4

REST

SharePoint

HTML

SASS

CSS

SQL

WORDPRESS

WEBPACK

ANALYTICAL SKILL

Hobbies

Cycling

Languages

English

Links

LinkedIn

GltHub

Porfolio

Courses

Fundamentals of React, Udemy

June 2020 — June 2020

ECMA-ECMAScript 2015 and TypeScript , Sages

November 2019 — November 2019

Internships

Quality Engineer at Delphi S.A., Kraków

July 2014 — August 2014

- · Work with technical documentation
- quality testing

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie danych osobowych zawartych w niniejszym dokumencie do realizacji procesu rekrutacji zgodnie z ustawą z dnia 10 maja 2018 roku o ochronie danych osobowych (Dz. Ustaw z 2018, poz. 1000) oraz zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).